Mss.B.St65p
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Caner, G. Colket, 1952
  - Caner, Harriet Frazier, 1951
  - Canivell, Francisco, 1946
  - Cannaday, John E., 1941
  - Cannon, Ida M., 1938
  - Cappel, Leona Rubinstein, 1940
  - Capper, Aaron, 1960
  - Capps, Richard B., 1945-1955
  - Carbide and Carbon Chemicals Corporation, 1947
  - Carey, Benjamin W., 1944
  - Carey, John, 1955-1957
  - Carey, Lawrence, 1959
  - Carey, Stephen G., 1960
  - Carey, William, 1947-1948
  - Carey, William B., 1949-1966
  - Carithers, Hugh A., 1952
  - Carlisle, M.C., 1947
  - Carlova, John, 1968
  - Carmichael, E. Arnold, 1956
  - Carmichael, Hugh T., 1949
  - Carmichael, J.R.T., 1940
  - Carmichael, Leonard, 1943-1944, 1961
  - Carnese, Rita, 1964
  - Caroli, Jacques, 1953
  - Carpenter, Howard Childs, 1936-1940, 1955-1961
  - Carroll, E.J., 1967
  - Carroll, Tain, 1960
  - Carroll, William V., 1946
  - Carrow, Robert, 1968
  - Carte, Estol Taylor, Jr., 1961
  - Carter, James P., 1963
  - Carver, Jean T., 1969
  - Cary, Stephen G., 1969
  - Caselli, Aldo, 1960
  - Cash, Ralph, 1958-1960
  - Cashman, James J., 1958
  - Cashore, William J., 1965
  - Casparis, Horton, 1940
  - Cassaday, George, 1959
  - Castillo, Fabio, 1952-1954
  - Castle, William B., 1968
  - Castro, Pedro Garcia, 1955
  - Catanese, Carl, 1964
  - Caum, Suzanne, 1952
  - Cavalli-Sforza, L.L., 1956
  - Cavelti, Philip A., 1946-1947
  - Cayley, C.K., 1950-1954
  - Ceballos Carrion, Alfredo, 1941-1966
  - Cecil, Henry S., 1955-1969; 2.0 folders
  - Cecil, Russell L., 1942-1943
  - CeCone, Alma, 1969
  - Cegielsky, John, 1947
  - Cervantes, Enriques J., 1942
  - Chafey, Virginia Stokes, 1956
  - Chalmers, A. Burns, 1958
  - Chalmers, Thomas, 1955
  - Chalmers, Thomas C., et al, 1963-1967
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1952
  - Chambers, Leslie A., 1941-1960
  - Chan, Janet, 1941
  - Chandler, Geoffrey, 1954
  - Chandra, Harish, 1956
  - Chang, Chang E., 1946
  - Chanutin, Alfred, 1954, 1961
  - Chaplin, Hugh, 1947, 1956-1957
  - Chapman, David M., 1970
  - Chapman, S. Stephen, 1955
  - Chapple, Alice, 1945
  - Chapple, Charles C., 1937-1971; 3.0 folders
  - Chapple, R.V., 1958
  - Chapple, Richard R., 1945
  - Char, Donald F.B., 1962
  - Charkes, N. David, 1962
  - Chatelaine, 1952
  - Chavis, Lawrence K., 1940
  - Chemical Abstracts, 1947
  - Chen, Ji, 1966-1967
  - Chenoweth, Alice D., 1941-1957
  - Chernick, Warren, 1961
  - Cherry, Napoleon, 1960
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad Company, 1947
  - Chesney, Jack, 1946
  - Chester, Allan G., 1948
  - Chester School District, 1952
  - Chevallier, Mr. and Mrs. Walter E., 1962
  - Chew, Pearl C., 1940
  - Chicago Convention Bureau, Inc., 1968
  - Child, Stanley R., 1947
  - Childs, Barton, 1961
  - Childs, Damon, 1966
    John N. Childs, and Charles G. Alhart.
  - Childs, Louise S., 1949-1951
  - Chipman, Sidney S., 1946
  - Chipps, H. Davis, 1957
  - Chopra, Joginder, 1958
  - Chow, Bacon F., 1954
  - Chown, Bruce, 1951-1953
  - Choy, Chung Hun, 1960
  - Christensen, Charles N., 1950-1961
  - Christensen, Elo, 1953
  - Christensen, Neil, 1948
  - Christian, Joseph R., 1965
  - Christie, Amos, 1952-1965
  - Christie, Keith A., 1962
  - Christman, Robert P., 1950
  - Christmas, T.W.E., 1948
  - Chumskov, M.P., Undated
  - Chung, Moon Yong, 1959
  - Church, Charles F., 1938-1944, 1971
  - Church, Clarence E., 1967
  - Churchill, Edward D., 1968
  - Chusie, Emanuel, 1953
  - Chute, A.L., 1955-1956
  - Ciliberti, Larry, 1962
  - Circulation, 1954
  - City Council, Philadelphia, 1948
  - City of New York, 1944
  - Civic Affairs, 1950
  - Civic Center, 1966
  - Civil Defense, 1950-1951
  - Clague, Dr. and Mrs. Ewan, 1957, 1969
  - Clark, Dean A., 1951-1956
  - Clark, Edith Earle, 1953, 1956
  - Clark, George R., 1952
  - Clark, Gerald R., 1966-1969
  - Clark, J.H., 1952
  - Clark, James Woodrow, 1951-1952
  - Clark, Joseph S., Jr., 1951-1968
    Mayor of Philadelphia; U.S. Senator from Pennsylvania.
  - Clark, Leon W., 1947
  - Clark, R.B., 1946
  - Clarke, Eleanor Stabler, 1968
  - Class of 1920, 1960-1972
  - Classen, Charles, 1949, 1952
  - Classen, Charles Henry, 1939-1941
  - Clausen, Samuel W., 1947
  - Clayton-Jones, E., 1961
  - Cleary, David M., 1956, 1966
  - Clement, David H., 1952-1959
  - Clement, Dorothy, 1959
  - Clements, F.W., 1953
  - Clinical Pediatrics, 1963
  - Clinical Pharmacology and Therapeutics, 1962
  - Clyde, Wallace A., 1941
  - Coates, George M., 1945-1959
  - Coates, John Boyd, Jr., 1958-1961
  - Cobau, Charles D., 1956
  - Cobb, Alice Littell, 1970-1971
  - Cobb, John C., 1956-1969
  - Cobb, Stanley, 1945-1946
  - Cobb, W. Montague, 1949, 1952
  - Cockburn, W. Charles, 1971
  - Cocks, Charles E., Jr., 1951
  - Coddington, Arthur, 1957
  - Cogan, Gilbert M., 1950-1951
  - Coggin, C. Joan, 1962
  - Coggins, Cecil H., 1964
  - Cohen, Abraham, 1952
  - Cohen, Daniel, 1966
  - Cohen, David, 1968
  - Cohen, Jacob, 1939
  - Cohen, Maynard, 1939-1940
  - Cohen, Morton E., 1940
  - Cohen, Norman N., 1959
  - Cohen, Robert, 1954-1967
  - Cohen, Seymour S., 1959-1972
  - Cohen, Sylvan M., 1963
  - Cohn, Edwin J., 1945-1953
  - Cohn, Frederick, 1956
  - Colburn, Harold L., 1966
  - Cole, Herbert L., 1966
    Abraham H. Topchik
  - Cole, John, 1961
  - Cole, Wyman C.C., 1955
  - Coleman, William T., 1953
  - Coles, Mrs. O. Hammond, 1970
  - Colket, Tristram C., 1952-1965
  - Collier, W. Edwin, 1947
  - Collings, Robert Z., Jr., 1956
  - Collins, Vernon L., 1951, 1960
  - Collins, William R., 1956
  - Collis, Robert, 1937
  - Collopy, P.J., 1940
  - Colomb, H.O., 1941
  - Colonna, Paul C., 1944, 1948
  - Colorado Department of Health, 1954
  - Colthirst, Ronald, 1952
  - Colton, Sabin W., 1959
  - Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS), 1946
  - Comens, Samuel N., 1946-1947
  - Comerci, George D., 1967-1968
  - Comprehensive Mental Health Plan, 1964-1965
  - Comroe, Bernard I., 1942-1945
  - Comroe, Julius H., 1951-1958
  - Conan, Neal J., 1950
  - Conard, Philip, 1941
  - Conard, Robert A., 1957
  - Conaway, James R., 1956
  - Concklin, Charles L., 1952-1953
  - Cone, Thomas E., Jr., 1953-1966
  - Congressional Correspondence, 1971
  - Conn, Howard F., 1955
  - Conn, Jerome W., 1969
  - Connecticut State Medical Journal, 1948
  - Connelly, Michael, 1970
  - Connor, Hilary J., 1956
  - Connor, William E., 1971
  - Conscientious Objectors, 1972
  - Conscription, 1944
  - Constant, Elizabeth R., 1945
  - Consumers' Committee, 1941
  - Conte, Andrew, 1949
  - Contemporary Club, 1948
  - Continental Casualty Company, 1960, 1968
  - Convey, John H., 1944
  - Conway, Donald C., 1966
  - Conway, Thomas, Jr., 1939
  - Cooch, Thomas, 1955-1968
  - Cook, Charles D., 1956, 1965
  - Cook, Mrs. E.B.M., 1957
  - Cook, E. Fullerton, 1939
  - Cooke, Jean V., 1941
  - Cooke, Robert E., 1958-1968
  - Colle, Mrs. R.M., 1953
  - Coombs, Harrison, 1949
  - Coon, R.J., III, 1961
  - Coons, Theodore W., 1971
  - Cooper, B. Hubert, 1960
  - Cooper, David Alexander, 1940-1961
  - Cooper, Gerald R., 1955
  - Cooper, Mrs. Kenneth, 1952
  - Cooper, M. M., 1952
  - Cope, E. Stanley P., 1961
  - Cope, Ellen, 1957, 1962
  - Cope, Oliver, 1947, 1965
  - Copeland, Solkin C., 1962
  - Coquerel, G., 1968
  - Cordero, Leticia S., 1951-1952
  - Coriell, Lewis L., 1946-1965, undated; 4.0 folders
  - Corlett, Keitha, 1960
  - Corneal, F. Bruce, 1948, 1953
  - Cornelison, C.E., 1953
  - Cornell, Virgil H., 1944
  - Cornell, Walter S., 1942, 1945, 1958-1959
  - Cornely, Donald A., 1957-1962
  - Corner, George W., 1964
  - Cornfeld, David, 1951-1965
  - Cornman, Henry D., III, 1955, 1957
  - Corpus Christi, Texas, 1959-1960
  - Correll, Paul, 1945
  - Corson, Bolton L., 1966, 1969
  - Corson, Samuel A., 1958-1965
  - Cosgriff, Stuart W., 1949
  - Cossa, John Paul, 1969-1970
  - Cossich, Carlos, 1962
  - Cossich, Olga Merida de, 1956
  - Cottrell, David C., 1970
  - Coulby, Margaret E., 1954
  - Coursin, David Baird, 1948-1958, 1969
  - Court, David, 1968-1969
  - Court, Donald, 1953, 1961
  - Court, S. Donald M., 1969
  - Court, Simon, 1969
  - Cowing, W.S., 1947
  - Cox, Becky C., 1954
  - Cox, David O., 1951, 1965
  - Cox, M. Armacost, 1945, 1948
  - Cox, Patrick J.N., 1960
  - Cox, Warren M., Jr., 1951
  - Coxe, Henry B., 1936
  - Coxe, Spencer, 1942
  - Craenen, Jo, 1959-1960
  - Craig, Howard Reid, 1941-1942, 1951
  - Craighill, Margaret D., 1943
  - Crawford, Charles B., 1939, 1941
  - Crawford, Dorothy B., 1940
  - Crawford, John, 1954
  - Crawford, Mary Newell, 1948-1957
  - Crawley, E.H., 1951
  - Cremen, Elmer, 1942
  - Cressman, Edith M., 1946
  - Cresson, Betty K., 1944
  - Cresson, Osborne Coates, 1941
  - Cresson, Samuel L., 1944-1951
  - Creveld, S. van, 1948-1951
  - The Crippled Child, 1942
  - Cristol, David S., 1952
  - Crocker, Edward, 1941
  - Crocker, Jane A., 1951
  - Cronk, Elwood F., 1958
  - Cronkite, Eugene P., 1961
  - Crooke, Nella and Sylvia, 1950-1951
  - Crosby, Edwin L., 1945
  - Crossan, Edward T., 1957
  - Crothers, Barbara A., 1962
  - Crothers, Bronson, 1950
  - Crowe, Aldrich, 1939-1943
  - Cruickshank, B., 1950
  - Cruickshank, Eric, 1952, 1960-1963
  - Cruickshank, Robert, 1945
  - Crump, Jean, 1948-1954
  - Crumpton, Mrs. Eric A., 1945
  - Crutcher, James C., 1962
  - Culbertson, Eugene C., 1954
  - Cullen, George L., 1964-1965
  - Cullen, Rose M., 1967
  - Culling, Alice E., 1946
  - Cullumbine, Harry, 1951
  - Cumings, Pierce, 1946
  - Cummings, Martin, 1965-1969
  - Cunningham, Robert, 1952
  - Curnen, Edward C., 1946-1953
  - Current Therapy, 1947, 1951
  - Curtin, Vincent T., 1942
  - Curtis, Homer C., 1945
  - Cusky, Walter, 1969
  - Cutting, Windsor, 1965-1967
  - Dabrowska, Mrs. Stephen, Undated
  - Daily, Edwin F., 1942
  - Dairy Council, Inc., 1949-1957
  - Dale, Grover C., 1947
  - Dallas, Constance H., 1954
  - Dalldorf, Gilbert, 1952, 1961-1962
  - Dalrymple, W. Howard, 1956-1957
  - Dam, Mr. and Mrs. Loring, 1968-1969
  - Dameshek, William, 1963-1966
  - Damrosch, Douglas S., 1948
  - Dancis, Joseph, 1950, 1961-1964
  - Danglov, S., 1959
  - Danks, David M., 1966
  - Dannenberg, Arthur, 1942, 1951-1955
  - Dannenberg, Arthur, Jr., 1941
  - Dannenberg, James L., 1957
  - Dannenberg, Marion, 1941
  - Danoff, Stuart, 1957
  - Danufsky, Philip G., 1956, 1969-1970
  - Dare, Martha V., 1968
  - Dargeon, Harold W., 1947
  - Darke, Roy A., 1941, 1944
  - Darlington, J.M., 1942
  - Darnell, Richard, 1958
  - Daroff, Joseph, 1948-1952, 1958
  - Darrow, Dan and Louise, 1963
  - Darrow, Daniel C., 1959
  - DaShiell, Mrs. Estelle, 1966
  - DaSilva, Martins, 1959
  - Daugherty, Silas C., 1961
  - Davenport, Fred M., 1957
  - Davidson, Charles S., 1949-1953
  - Davidson, Douglas T., 1940-1962
  - Davidson, Leonard T., 1953
  - Davidson, Murray, 1956
  - Davies, John A.V., 1942
  - Davies, William E., 1963
  - Davis, Addison, 1944
  - Davis, Eleanor Bushnell, 1941
  - Davis, George Cresswell, 1949
  - Davis, Hallowell, 1968
  - Davis, Harold L., 1947-1958
  - Davis, Harriet, 1948-1954
  - Davis, John E., 1962
  - Davis, Junius, 1953
  - Davis, Junius W., Jr., 1951
  - Davis, True, 1958
  - Davis, Mrs. Wendel H., 1952
  - Davison, Wilburt C., 1940-1962
  - Dawley, Almena, 1951
  - Dawson, Harris P., 1941, 1944
  - Dawson, Kathryn M., 1952
  - Day, Richard L., 1958-1969
  - Dayton, Mr. and Mrs. William B., 1956
  - Deamer, William C., 1954-1956, 1964
  - Dean, James Seay, 1949-1952
  - Dean, Joseph O., 1960
  - Dean, Wynant, 1948
  - Dearden, John E., 1939
  - Dearing, W.P., 1968
  - Deasey, Agnes, 1944
  - DeAyala, Belita, 1959, 1962
  - DeBelle, J.E., 1945
  - Debre, Robert, 1947-1958, 1965-1966
  - Dechert, Robert, 1968
  - Decker, John, 1957
  - Decker, John L., 1949, 1969
  - Dees, J.M., Jr., 1965
  - Defendi, Christel C., 1958
  - Defense, Council of, 1942
  - Degkwitz, Rudolf, 1947-1948
  - Deh, Du Swun, 1939
  - Dehne, T.L., 1955
  - Deinhardt, Friedrich, 1955-1971
  - Deisher, Robert W., 1957
  - Deitrick, John, 1965
  - DeJong, J. David, 1953
  - DeKruif, Paul, 1935-1942; 2.0 folders
  - De la Torre, Joaquin A., 1941-1964
  - Delaware Medical Journal, 1970
  - Delchester Farms, 1932-1934
  - DeLeeuw, N.K.M., 1968
  - Delfino, Alejandro Rodriguez, 1955
  - DeLien, H., 1959
  - DeMar, Vickie, 1963
  - Deming, Margery van N., 1948, 1950
  - Demlow, Jack H., 1959
  - Demmy, Merlyn R., 1966
  - DeMohrenschildt, George, 1963
  - Dempsher, William, 1961
  - Denison, George L., 1949
  - Denniston, Joseph C., 1965-1967
  - Denoon, Eleanor K., 1970
  - Denton, R.L., 1953
  - Denton, Robert, 1958-1962; 2.0 folders
  - DeRentis, Mrs. Nick, 1950
  - DeRose, Mrs. Rosalind, 1967
  - DeSilverio, Robert V., 1965-1966
  - Desjardins, Paul, 1968-1969
  - DeToni, Giovanni, 1954-1955
  - Detwiler, Helen L., 1965
  - Deutsch, Ilka, 1941
  - Devereaux, Mrs. Charles, 1943
  - Devereux Schools, 1948, 1954
  - Dewees, Mr. and Mrs. Lovett, 1941-1948, 1967-1969
  - Dewees, Robert L., 1946, 1953-1957
  - Dewey, Edward B., 1939
  - DeWitt, Nicholas, 1954
  - Dexter, Sidney B., 1952-1953, 1966
  - Diamond, Louis K., 1940-1956
  - Dible, J. Henry, 1953
  - Dick, George, 1959-1969
  - Dick, H. Lenox H., 1949
  - Dickinson, John, 1941-1942
  - Dicks, Russell L., 1954
  - Dickson, Roger W., 1950-1951
  - Dickstein, Benjamin, 1946-1967
  - Dicta-Records, Inc., 1942
  - Diemer, Miss, 1948
  - Dietrich, Mr. and Mrs. H. Richard, 1945, 1950
  - Dietrich, Herbert J., 1959
  - Dietrich, Kathleen, 1961
  - Dietrich, W.S., 1960
  - Dietrick, Dr., 1960
  - Dilworth, Margaret, 1944
  - Dilworth, Mr. and Mrs. Richardson, 1947-1970
  - DiMoia, Frank and Margaret Mary, 1961-1968
  - Dingle, John H., 1946, 1951
  - Dinofer, Mrs. Sidney, 1955
  - Dintenfass, Henry, 1948
  - Directory of Medical Specialists, 1959, 1963, 1971-1972
  - DiSilvestro, Anthony J., 1961
  - Dismukes, Nancy Lee, 1941
  - Distler, Edward K., 1959
  - Diwany, M., 1956, 1960
  - Dixon, James P., 1952, 1969-1971
  - Djerassi, Isaac, 1959-1968; 3.0 folders
  - Doan, Charles A., 1955
  - Doane, Joseph C., 1939, 1951-1965
  - Dobkin, Harris, 1957
  - Dobson, Donald, 1950
  - Docter, Jack M., 1960
  - Dodds, Paul, 1941
  - Dodge, Milton, 1952-1953
  - Dods, Sir Lorimer, 1953-1959, 1970
  - Dogramaci, Ihsan, 1961
  - Dohan, F. Curtis, 1950-1951, 1969
  - Dohmen, A., 1947
  - Dolan, John E., 1958
  - D'Olies, M., 1966
  - Dolora, Sister Mary, 1965-1969
  - Domincovitch, H.A., 1940-1944
  - Donaldson, James B., 1966
  - Donnan, Stuart, 1961
  - Donner, William H., 1946
  - Donovan, W.M., 1940-1941
  - Dooley, Richard R., 1952
  - Dooley, Samuel, 1955
  - Dorman, George W., 1953
  - Dornan, William J., 1946-1947
  - Dorr, Mrs. C.C., 1942
  - Dorrance, John T., 1953
  - Dorrance, William R., 1952
  - Dotterer, John E., 1941-1942
  - Dougherty, F.M., 1948
  - Douglas, William O., 1958
  - Doval, John H., 1942
  - Dove, Jeannette, 1947
  - Dowling, Harry F., 1956
  - Downes, Virginia, 1951
  - Downie, Allan W., 1966
  - Downward, Nella, 1943
  - Doyle, John A., 1952
  - Dozzi, Daniel L., 1941
  - Drabkin, David L., 1952, 1966
  - Drake, Miles E., 1951-1957, 1966
  - Drayer, Calvin Searle, 1957
  - Dresden, Arnold, 1951
  - Drinker, Henry M., 1950-1953, 1965
  - Drinker, Henry S., 1963
  - Dripps, Robert D., 1950-1952, 1966
  - Driscoll, Mrs. Richard, 1962-1968
  - Driscoll, Patrick, 1962
  - Driscoll, Richard H., 1966
  - Driscoll, Shirley G., 1951-1952
  - Duane, Julia McElhinney, 1955-1959
  - Duane, Morris, 1969
  - Duane, Thomas D., 1965-1969
  - DuBarry, Joseph, 1939, 1948-1949
  - Dubin, I.N., 1958
  - Dublin, Thomas D., 1945
  - DuBois, Arthur B., 1969
  - DuBois, Joseph J., 1951
  - DuBois, Robert, 1963
  - Ducci, Hector, 1949-1952
  - Ducharme, Jacques R., 1956-1965
  - Duckers, Marion, 1948
  - Dudgeon, Mr. and Mrs. J. Alastair, 1950, 1960-1968
  - Duenas-Lehman, Alvaro, 1966
  - Duffy, Philip, 1951
  - Dugid, William M., 1961
  - Duguid, John, 1951
  - Duk, Jin Yun, 1958
  - Dukes, Mrs. Barbara, 1941
  - Dull, H. Bruce, 1968
  - Dunbar, Flanders, 1942
  - Duncan, Garfield G., 1946, 1952-1959
  - Dunham, Ellen Douglas, 1940
  - Dunham, Ethel C., 1939, 1943
  - Dunlap, George A., 1965, 1968
  - Dunlop, Stuart G., 1960
  - Dunn, Frank J., 1969
  - Dunn, Mrs. J. Struthers, 1954
  - Dunphy, Donal L., 1947
  - DuPont, Mrs. A.C., 1941
  - DuPont, Lammot, 1952
  - DuPont de Nemours, E.I. and Company, 1957
  - Dupper, O.M., 1952
  - Dye, Dewey A., 1952
  - Dyer, R.E., 1941
  - Dyer, W. Wallace, 1943, 1966
  - Eagle, Harry, 1955
  - Eagles, Archie Y., 1951
  - Earl, Robert P., 1956-1957
  - Easter Seal Campaign, 1963-1965
  - Eaton, Monroe D., 1942
  - Eberle, Anna, 1946-1952
  - Eberlein, Walter R., 1955-1964
  - Ecker, E.E., 1951
  - Eckert, Philip A., 1957
  - Eckhardt, Richard D., 1948
  - Eckley, George M., 1946-1950
  - Eckman, Albert R., 1948
  - Eczaclbasl, Sakir, 1961-1962
  - Edelson, Morris, 1949
  - Edsall, Geoffrey, 1956, 1961
  - Edwards, John Hilton, 1960, 1963
  - Edwards, Earle, 1965-1966
  - Edwards, Walter M., 1963
  - Edwards, Walton, 1942-1954
  - Egan, James T. and Anne I., 1961
  - Eglick, Paul G., 1949-1959
  - Ehrenzeller Citation, 1963
  - Ehrich, William E., 1952, 1968
  - Ehrlich, J.W., 1951, 1956
  - Ehrlich, S. Paul, 1967
  - Eichelberger, Eli, 1953
  - Eichenwald, Heinz F., 1955-1961
  - Eichna, Ludwig, 1970
  - Eilers, Robert D., 1969
  - Einhorn, Nathan H., 1941-1968
  - Eisenberg, Leon, 1946, 1962-1967
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1960
  - Eisenhower, John, 1969
  - Eisenhower, Milton S., 1952
  - Eisenoff, Henry, 1948
  - Eisman, H.P., 1968
  - Eisner, Henry, 1959
  - Elderkin, Francis Michael, 1961
  - Electronic Tube Corporation, 1947
  - Elfman, Ethel, Undated
  - Eliot, Johan W., 1955
  - Eliot, Martha M., 1942-1960
  - Elizondo, J. Gonzalez, 1946-1947
  - Elkerton, L.E., 1952
  - Elkington, Peter, 1965
  - Elkinton, Anna G., 1946
  - Elkinton, David C., 1963
  - Elkinton, J. Passmore, 1955
  - Elkinton, J. Russell, 1942-1946, 1964-1971
  - Elkinton, Thomas W., 1958
  - Elliott, Frank A., 1971
  - Elliott, Willard B., 1960
  - Ellis, John, 1945
  - Ellis, William J., 1938
  - Elsom, Katharine, 1942, 1965
  - Elsom, Kendall A., 1941-1947, 1957
  - Elsom, George Y., 1946-1947
  - El Taher, Fousad D., 1956
  - Ely, Gertrude, 1968
  - Ely, R. Cannon, 1947, 1954
  - Ely, Robert S., 1959
  - Emerson, Richard P., 1962
  - Emerson, Sumner B., 1946
  - Emery, Beverly, 1968-1969
  - Emery, K.E., 1965
  - Emich, John P., 1968
  - Emlen, J. Merritt, 1967
  - Emlen, John, 1943-1945
  - Emlen, John T., Jr., 1946-1952, 1960-1969
  - Emlen, Samuel, 1961-1966
  - Empey, Lucas W., 1954
  - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1946-1951
  - Enders, John F., 1944-1971; 2.0 folders
  - Enders, John F. and Elizabeth Maris, 1943-1946; 5.0 folders
  - English-Speaking Union, 1960-1962
  - Enloe, Cortez F., Jr., 1964
  - Ennis, Herbert L., 1967
  - Entwhistle, Marlyn, 1942
  - Entwistle, George, 1970
  - Ephraim, Shirley, 1952
  - Epstein, Franklin H., 1967
  - Epstein, Harold G., 1950
  - Erdman, William J., II, 1962, 1967
  - Erickson, Leif, 1957
  - Eriksen, George N., Jr., 1947
  - Ernst, Lida, 1946
  - Erslev, Allan J., 1969
  - Esterson, Sherman H., 1957
  - Estes, Harry M., 1940, 1945
  - Esty, Geoffrey W., 1942
  - Ettinger, Richard H., 1953
  - Evans, Alton Norman, 1948-1955
  - Evans, Anna R., 1967, 1971
  - Evans, Audrey E., 1971
  - Evans, Francis C., 1941-1942
  - Evans, Harold E., 1948-1954, 1966
  - Evans, Henry C., 1964
  - Evans, Jonathan, 1961-1962
  - Evans, Katharine W., 1942-1948
  - Evans, Mrs. Henry, 1957
  - Evans, Philip, Undated
  - Evans, Robert L., 1964
  - Evans, Thomas H., 1959
  - Evans, William E., 1959
  - Evening Bulletin, Undated
  - Eves, Curtis, 1941
  - Ewing, Mrs. Charles, 1949
  - Ewing, David Q., 1940
  - Excerpta Medica, 1947
  - Exline, A.L., 1951-1965
  - Faber, Harold K., 1940-1971
  - Fabiyi, Akinyele, 1956-1961
  - Faherty, John C., 1945
  - Fahnestock, Herbert I., 1957
  - Fair, Gordon M., 1947-1948
  - Fairbank, John K., 1971
  - Fairchild, John P., 1961
  - Fairhall, Lawrence F., 1943
  - Fairlie, Lillian, 1951
  - Fake, Mrs. Frank C., 1968
  - Faktoroff, Ruth, 1966
  - Falconer, Mr. and Mrs. Douglas, 1966-1969, undated
  - Fallon, Richard N., 1946-1947
  - Fanconi, Guido, 1947-1960
  - Fanger, Herbert, 1951
  - Fanjul, Harry G., 1960
  - Farago, Peter J., 1955
  - Farber, Harold I., 1949-1950
  - Farber, Herman W., 1942
  - Farber, Sidney, 1942-1956
  - Farga, Nieves H., 1955-1956
  - Farlee, Bernice B., 1950
  - Farley, J.W., 1953
  - Farquhar, John, 1950, 1958-1959
  - Farr, Lee E., 1942-1948
  - Farr, Richard S., 1963
  - Farrar, George E., 1955-1965
  - Farrell bill, 1945
  - Farrell, Charles F., 1965
  - Farrier, Lillie C. Walker, 1947-1950
  - Fasanella, Rocko M., 1946
  - Fashena, Gladys J., 1958
  - Fastier, L.B., 1949
  - Fay, Marian, 1945
  - Fay, Temple, 1943
  - Fayer, Harry J., 1945
  - Faz-Tabio, Humberto, 1964
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1941
  - Federal Security Agency, 1950, 1952
  - Feghai, A., 1958
  - Feinstein, Aaron A., 1966
  - Feinstein, Norman B., 1965
  - Feirer, William A., 1946, 1971
  - Feiser, William H., 1943
  - Feldman, Roger Allen, 1959-1963
  - Felice, Mrs. C.W.W., 1955
  - Fellowships, 1946-1957; 2.0 folders
  - Felton, Harriet M., 1949-1963
  - Fendrick, Gerald M., 1968-1970
  - Fenercioglu, Ali Riza, 1952-1953
  - Fenichel, Benjamin, 1946
  - Fennell, Mrs. L., 1955
  - Fenner, Frank, 1949-1953
  - Ferebee, Shirley H., 1954
  - Ferguson, James Henry, 1961
  - Ferguson, Joseph C., 1967
  - Ferguson, L. Kraeer, 1944-1946
  - Ferguson, Robert G., 1955
  - Ferleger, Harry, 1966
  - Ferris, Shirley, 1971
  - Fesl, Mrs. Nick, Undated
  - Fetter, Theodore R., 1948
  - Fewell, Alexander G., 1944-1952
  - Field, Edward G., 1947-1950
  - Field, Elaine C., 1963
  - Field, John B., 1951-1952
  - Fields, Harry, 1944-1945
  - Figueroa, Etervina, 1952
  - Figueroa de Gonzales, Miguel, 1955-1956
  - Filho, Clementino Fraga, 1951
  - Finberg, Laurence, 1967
  - Findlay, G.M., 1952
  - Fine, Hyman P., 1949
  - Fine, John S., 1950, 1952
  - Finkelstein, David, 1960
  - Finkelstein, Herman, 1959
  - Finkelstein, Jack, 1960-1962
  - Finkelstein, Marie, 1943
  - Finland, Maxwell, 1958
  - Finnegan, John L., 1955
  - Finnerty, Frank, 1965
  - Firestone, George M., 1952
  - Firestone, Roger S., 1963
  - Fischer, Alfred E., 1953
  - Fischer, Carl C., 1941-1969
  - Fischer, Doane C., 1953-1955
  - Fischer, Enid May, 1953
  - Fischer, H. Keith, 1959
  - Fish, Sylvan M., 1962
  - Fishbein, Morris, 1965
  - Fisher, A. Murray, 1949, 1960
  - Fisher, Carolyn A., Undated
  - Fisher, Fred, 1948
  - Fisher, John A., 1958-1962
  - Fisher, Olivia, 1959
  - Fisher, Peter, 1947
  - Fisher, Wilton M., 1962
  - Fishman, Alfred P., 1970
  - Fitts, Barbara K., 1952-1953
  - Fitts, Francis M., 1958
  - Fitzgerald, John, 1946
  - Fitzhardinge, Pamela M., 1959-1962
  - Fitz-Hugh, Thomas, Jr., 1938, 1942
  - Flancer, Marvin, 1967
  - Fleck, W.H.K., 1961
  - Fleckenstine, R. Jean, 1955
  - Fleet, William Floyd, 1958-1961
  - Fleisher, Daniel S., 1959
  - Fleisher, Robert H., 1967
  - Fleming, Agnes A., 1955
  - Fleming, Alexander, 1945
  - Fleming, Arthur W., 1962-1963
  - Fleming, Elizabeth P., 1933
  - Fleming, Martha E., 1952-1953
  - Fletcher, Bernice, 1965
  - Flick, Jean L., 1946
  - Flick, John, 1949-1951
  - Flinker, David, 1957
  - Flinn, Lewis B., 1950-1966
  - Flinn, Waldo, 1939
  - Floer, Ingeborg, 1953
  - Flood, R.E., 1962
  - Florida Department of Health, 1957
  - Florman, Alfred L., 1950-1960
  - Flosdorf, Earl W., 1946-1954
  - Fluck, David A., 1966
  - Foesel, C.B., 1944
  - Fogarty, John E., 1961
  - Fogel, Bernard J., 1965
  - Fogelson, M. Harold, 1961
  - Foldes, Elizabeth, 1947
  - Folsom, Marion B., 1965
  - Fomon, Samuel Joseph, 1949-1954, 1967
  - Food and Drug Administration, 1955, 1959
  - Ford, Bacon and Davis, 1946
  - Ford, Lillian, 1957
  - Foreign Guests, 1959
  - Forer, Robert, 1943
  - Forfar, John O., 1949-1962